Art Collins Papers ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop [RESTRICTED], 1985-2005, undated
  - "Passenger," Spanish phones, 2004 July 6 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Shake Appeal," Lacoste Statue of Liberty Fund, 2004 June (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "Lust For Life," Billionaire, 2004 May (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "Passenger," "Lust For Life," Ultimate Rock, 2004 May 14 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Elektra statement, Janine Natter letter, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Elektra statement, September, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "Passenger," Expedition Österreich, Vol. 1, 2004 July 6 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "Lust For Life," EMI Gold - Rock Box, 2004 May 14 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - David Bowie: A Reality Tour, 2004 May 13 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Verizon Wireless voiceovers, 2004 April (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Fat Possum Junior Kimbrough tribute, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - "China Girl," HBO Sopranos, 1998 July 29 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Rock Heroes Live, 2004 January 15 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Top 100 Artists of Rock and Roll, 1998 July 23 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - "Feel in Love With Me," Stupid Kids, 1998 August (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "Lust For Life," licensing, 1998, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - "Moonlight Lady," Heavy in Love, 2004 January 8 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - "Nightclubbing," Banana Republic, 1998 July (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "Nightclubbing," Virgin France, 1998 July 31 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - "Passenger," licensing, 1998, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - "Private Hell," Glow, 2004 January 8 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Iggy Pop: Wild American, South Bank Show, TV, 1998 March 24 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Winner and Losers," Miami Vice, 1998 July 1 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Day in the Garden, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Jacoves, Aaron, 1998 March 2 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Doctor Music Festival, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Front Pages, merchandise, magazine covers, 1998 March 31 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Graz date, 1998 February (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Highland Festival, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Hurricane Festival, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Jim and Suchi agreement [CLOSED], 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    This material is CLOSED until the death of Iggy Pop. Access to this material is unavailable until that time.
  - July German date, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - MS 45, Talent House, 1998 June 8 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Jacobson, Natalie, information, circa 1998 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Dubreuille, Phillippe, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - "Rock Show," Winter X Games 2004, 2003 November 24 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Roskilde, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean, 2003 December 23 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Siemens (Germany), 1998 June 29 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Sweetwaters Festival, 1998 August 10 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Swiss gig, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "China Girl," Wedding Singer, Bug Music and other licensing, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Shoreline Music Festival production directory, circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Instinct press, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - A&M press, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Canada, press, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Tourstar, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Nice Man Merchandising, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Brockum, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Creative Artists Agency, Pretenders and other concerts / tours, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Europe tour, 1986 (Japan and Pretenders tour), 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Tour insurance, 1986 August 21 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Europe tour, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Japan tour, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Pretenders tour, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - UK tour, merchandise, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Tour budget, income, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Status reports, 1986, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - USA tour, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Sales figures, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Tour data, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Grammy's file, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Various photographs and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    File also contains three pieces of fan mail.
  - JLM information, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - USA tour, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - A&M Records, Iggy Pop: Live At the Ritz video, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "Isolation" video, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - "Cry For Love" video, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Recording information, Blah-Blah-Blah, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - "Cry For Love" information, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Cry Baby information, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Charts and sales figures, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Bug Music royalties and figures, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Credits, Blah-Blah-Blah, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - New album information, Instinct, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - South American tour, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Tour rider, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Relativity Records distribution, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - AEI, Lydia Hilton, 1987 August (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Sakamoto attorney information, re: "Risky", 1987 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Jones, Steve, 1986 July 31 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Knopf, Alfred, contract, 1987 March (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - A&M contract, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Westwood One contract, 1987 April (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Press information, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Agreements and contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Latin America tour, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Press, July, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Band per diem receipts, 1988 February 16 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Producer, Iggy Pop agreement, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Tribute to Disney Music album contract, "Family Affair" / "Purple Haze" budget, circa 1985, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Studio information Instinct sessions, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Recording schedule Instinct sessions, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - American Federation of Musicians contract [RESTRICTED], 1988 March (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - International press, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - JLM management, press, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Creative Artists Agency, accounting, 1988 July (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Budget information, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Bug Music, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Donahue, David, documentary, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Financial receipts, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - JLM management, bills, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - JLM management, Iggy Pop status report, 1986 September-1986 December (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - JLM management, Iggy Pop status report, 1987 January-1987 April (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Foreign press / miscellaneous articles, 1986 (Box OS1, Folder 2, Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Foreign press magazines, 1990, 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - A&M, Blah, Blah, Blah, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Press photos [photocopies], 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1986 (Box OS1, Folder 2, Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1988 (Box OS1, Folder 3, Box 17, Folder 11-12)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 13-18, Box OS1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1995 (Box OS1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1996 (Box OS2, Folder 1, Box 17, Folder 19-24)
  - Miscellaneous articles / press, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Iggy Pop / Henry Rollins with Paula Greif and Art Collins, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Iggy Pop photos with correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous promotional material, 1988, 1994-1999 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Avenue B and live reviews, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - L'Uomo Vogue annotated with related photographs, 1998 March (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Magazines, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous presskits, publications, and correspondence, 1987, 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Iguanas, Tijuana gig, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Tour contracts, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - William Morris Agency contracts, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
  - Handwritten letter from Iggy Pop to Guns n' Roses [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1, Box 18, Folder 12)
    This original letter is closed. Patrons must use digital or physical facsimiles of originals. Use of originals only by permission of the Head Archivist, Library and Archives, Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum.
  - Fan mail and charity requests, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 13-21)
  - Biography and lyrics, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995, 2005, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1993-2000, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Mailing information [RESTRICTED], 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Financial records and correspondence, 1999, 2004-2005, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Licensing information, 1999, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tour schedules and contracts [RESTRICTED] (Box 19, Folder 7-9)
  - EMI DVD Live At the Avenue B and box set Million in Prizes [RESTRICTED], 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - E-mail correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Includes video footage stored on a CD-R of Iggy Pop meeting Madonna and performing on stage in Dublin.
  - Band documents [RESTRICTED], 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Virgin license agreement, 1999 September 28 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Music video distribution, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Bug Music report, 2004 October-2004 December (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Musicologist report Passenger, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Series II: Marianne Faithfull [RESTRICTED], Bulk, 1992-1997; 1983, 1987-1997, undated
  Series II: Marianne Faithfull contains contracts, professional and personal correspondence, tour information, clippings, and album and licensing information, including documents related to Faithfull’s Secret Life album and tour, and her autobiography. The files are arranged as received by the donor. Some material has been stored separately due to size and condition concerns.
  Some of the materials in this series are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Coombes, Ian, correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Cultural Industry, Seven Deadly Sins proposal, 1995 July (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Ossard, Claudie, correspondence, 1995 June (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Outstanding Island press requests, 1995 July (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Lewis, J.T., correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Band information and equipment, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Royalties, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Tracking [RESTRICTED], 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25-26)
    These files include correspondence, financial records, tour, and performance information.
  - Producer and booking contracts, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Autobiography, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Rock Hall, talent release, 1994 November 17 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Tour budget and press, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 30-31)
  - Island address change, 1995 July 10 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Squeeze compilation LP, 1995 June 2 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Cantor, Arthur, correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Bratton, Hillary, correspondence, 1995 August 10 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Ogilvy and Mather correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Jones, Brian, movie, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Jagger, Mick, correspondence, 1992 November 25 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Coombes, Ian - royalty statement, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Australia information, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Barney's Clothes, 1995 February 5 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - AIDS Project Los Angeles - Bernie Taupin, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - American Airlines [RESTRICTED], 1994 October 11 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Tam, Dr., correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Nole, Sam, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music / Marianne Faithfull bill for car, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Grand Funk Railroad reunion, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Howard Tose, 1995 November 13 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Harvard gig, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Press, 1987, 1989-1995 (Box OS2, Folder 2, Box 20, Folder 6-7)
  - Television documentaries, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rosaril script, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - New album [ Secret Life], 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Studio budget, Angelo Badalamenti correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lamblot, Bertrand, correspondence, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lyrics, 1992-1995 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
    Includes a demo tape of "Something Marvelous."
  - Movie requests, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, 1994 July (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - EMI International CD-ROM idea, 1995 March 10 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - City of Lost Children, 1995 November 9 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Island spoken word label, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Blazing Away, Incorporated, 1993, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Lighting companies, 1995 July (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Faithfull, Marianne, letters of complaint, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Faithfull, Marianne, general, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Baker, Martin, Marianne Faithfull documentary, 1995 October (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Miami Light Project, 1995 November 28 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Dutch radio, Kurt Weill, 1995 November 21 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - When Pigs Fly review, 1995 November 10 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - First Avenue gig cost, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - 20th Century Pop, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Mann, Roberto, correspondence, 1995 December 12 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Financial [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 32-33)
  - Travel, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Touring, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Set list, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Publishing, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Licensing, 1995 August (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Angelo Badalamenti correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Passport information, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Montreux Jazz Festival, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Chieftains, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Talent agency contracts, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 43-44)
  - Brooklyn Philharmonic Orchestra, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Press, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Crossing Border Festival, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Weiman Cabaret", 1995 March (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - European tour, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Oxford Union, 1995 November 7 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Seven Deadly Sins, Brooklyn Philharmonic Orchestra, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Solo contract, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Promotion, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Marketing, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Bios, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - International press, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1983, 1994, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Video production and touring, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Series III: Art Collins Personal [RESTRICTED], Bulk, 1972-2005; 1964, 1972-2005, undated
  Series III: Art Collins Personal contains material relating to Collins’ personal and business life (outside of his relations with Iggy Pop and Marianne Faithfull), including correspondence, photographs, clippings, ephemera, film scripts, publications, tax information, invoices, orders, travel information, and family information. The files are arranged as received by the donor. Some material has been stored separately due to size and condition concerns.
  Some of the materials in this series are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Some material in this series is CLOSED until the death of Nikki Collins. Access to this material is unavailable until that time. The condition of some of the audiovisual materials in this series has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of the audiovisual materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Subseries 1: Film Scripts, 1990-1996, 2002, undated
    Scope and Contents
    Subseries 1: Film Scripts contains complete scripts sent to Collins for consideration by his clients. Scripts are arranged alphabetically by screenwriter, or by title when no screenwriter's name was available.
    - Antle, Spencer, Escapist, undated (Box 21, Object 13)
    - Asshole, undated (Box 21, Object 14)
    - Batali, Dean, Adventures of Pete and Pete, 1995 November 3 (Box 21, Object 15)
    - Behr, Melissa and Sherrie Rose, Me and Will with letter to Iggy Pop, 1996 (Box 21, Object 16)
    - De Luca, Michael, Freddy's Dead: Final Nightmare, 1990 (Box 21, Object 17)
    - DeJoseph, Dominic, Tarred and Feathered, 1994 July 5 (Box 21, Object 18)
    - Depp, D.P. and Johnny Depp, Brave, 1996 June (Box 21, Object 19)
    - Donnhofer, Deigo, Virgin, 1994 (Box 21, Object 20)
    - Feuer, Stuart and Laurent Rejito, Country Heritage, 1996 (Box 21, Object 21)
    - Gilligan, Vince, Home Fries, 1993 February 25 (Box 21, Object 22)
    - Goyer, David S., Crow: City of Angels, 1995 (Box 21, Object 23)
    - Hodge, John, Trainspotting with correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Object 24)
    - Levy, Jefrey, Et Tu, Babe, undated (Box 21, Object 25)
    - Lovedog, Cheri and Robin Whitehouse, Prey for Rock and Roll with press release and correspondence, 2002 (Box 21, Object 26)
    - Mahon, Maureen and Nicholas Monahan, Thirteenth Floor, 1996 October 30 (Box 21, Object 27)
    - Roisentul, Gary J. and Darin Bennett, Regards from Hell, 1996 August (Box 21, Object 28)
    - Ransom, 1995 June 1 (Box 21, Object 29)
    - Rose, Daniel R., Wayne County Ramblin', 1992 May 23 (Box 21, Object 30)
    - Sarafian, Tedi, Tank Girl, 1993 December 10 (Box 21, Object 31)
    - Soodik, Trish, Shake, Rattle and Rock, 1994 April 29 (Box 21, Object 32)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, Photographs, and Ephemera [RESTRICTED], 1978, 1981-2005, undated
    Subseries 2: Correspondence, Photographs, and Ephemera contains personal and professional correspondence, personal and professional photographs, and ephemera collected by Art Collins. Some files concern artists seeking representation or presenting songs for Collins' clients. Material is arranged as received by donor. Some material is stored separately due to size and condition concerns, or because the material is currently CLOSED to researchers.
    Some of the materials in this subseries are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. The condition of some of the audiovisual materials in the collection has not yet been determined for playback purposes and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available. Other material in this series is CLOSED until the death of Nikki Collins. Access to this material is unavailable until that time. Specific restrictions are noted at the file folder level.
    - Iggy Pop and Stooges, 1990, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      Includes a letter from Matt Groening to Iggy Pop regarding the June 2003 All Tomorrow's Parties Festival, a letter from Scott Asheton's wife inquiring about the possibility of a Stooges reunion, a letter from David Fricke of Rolling Stone, and photographs by Petra Arnold.
    - Rolling Stones, 1978, 1981-1984, undated (Box OS2, Folder 3, Object 2, Box 21, Folder 34)
      Includes letter from Bill Graham Productions regarding promotion of new album, Tattoo You.
    - Relix, 1978 July 24 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Monck, Chip, press kit, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Earthlink [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - McGee, David, schedule, 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Mexican retirement ideas, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Grammy tickets, Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction ceremony invitation, 1989, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Behind the Music: Peter Tosh, 1999 August (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Mojo Wall of Sound photocards, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - McLagan, Ian, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Radio Crystal Blue, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Maverick, World Champion Magician press kit, 1996 August 24 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Connelly, Chris, 1994 November 22 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Escovedo, Alejandro, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - LaCasio, Anna, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Carrizo, Alejandra, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Neel, K.C. [RESTRICTED], 1998 March 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      The condition of the audiocassette in this file has not yet been determined for playback purposes and is, therefore, RESTRICTED. An access copy of this item may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
      Includes audiocassette of song "I Want" by KC Neel.
    - Capitano, Nick, 1996, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      Includes self-titled CD by Reign of Sound.
    - Ether Park, 1998 December 21 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Grauer, George [RESTRICTED], 1998 June 25 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Includes audiocassette of song "Be Good to Yourself" by Bill Stewart and George Grauer.
    - Loosigian, Billy, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Includes self-titled CD by Nervous Eaters.
    - Marino, Nora / Cleo No More [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      Includes self-titled audiocassette by Cleo No More.
    - McCarthy, John Michael / Big Broad Guerrilla Monster, Incorporated [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      Includes audiocassette with original music for IggyZiggy by Tim Feleppa and Archie Mueller.
    - Miscellaneous, 1988, 1992-2005, undated (Box OS2, Folder 3, Object 1, Box 22, Folder 16-18)
      Includes backstage passes, holiday cards, e-mail, personal photos, photocopy of James Dean death certificate, various articles printed from the internet, and travel brochures.
    - Collins, Art and Nikki [CLOSED], circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      This material is CLOSED until the death of Nikki Collins. Access to this material is unavailable until that time.
  - Subseries 3: Publications and Clippings, 1964, 1972-2000, undated
    Subseries 3: Publications and Clippings includes materials related to Collins' clients, such as Iggy Pop, or areas of personal interest, including the Beatles and Elvis Presley. A number of clippings related to the Rolling Stones from 1978 and 1981, are included, presumably collected during Collins' time at Rolling Stones Records. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by artist.
    - Beatles and related, 1964, 1974-2000 (Box OS5, Folder 1, Box 22, Folder 19, Box OS3, Box OS4)
    - Fluid, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Harper, Ben, 1999 August (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Pop, Iggy, 1990, 1998-1999, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Presley, Elvis, 1977, 1981 (Box OS5, Folder 1)
    - Rolling Stones, 1972, 1978-2000,undated (Box 22, Folder 23-28, Box OS4, Folder 2, Box OS6, Folder 1, Box OS5)
    - Various, 1974, 1979-1997 (Box 22, Folder 29, Box OS2, Folder 4, Box OS5, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Audiovisual Materials [RESTRICTED], Bulk, 1980-1998; 1967-1998, undated
  The condition of some of the audiovidual materials in this series has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the series are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.